<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Recipe</string>
    <string name="txt"><br>Ingredients:\n</br>

 <br>-3 cups half-boiled polao rice\n</br>
 <br>-1 cup kalaiyera dal\n</br>
 <br>- Baking soda\n</br>
 <br>-1 teaspoon salt\n</br>
 <br>-1/2 teaspoon sugar\n</br>
 <br>- 1 cup of boiled potatoes\n</br>
 <br>- 1/2 cup steamed peas\n</br>
 <br>- Chop the onion as desired\n</br>
 <br>-One pinch or a pinch of whole cumin\n</br>
 <br>-Yellow chilli coriander cumin powder a little\n</br>
 <br>A pinch of hing (even if you don\'t give it)\n</br>
 <br>-Coriander leaves and raw chilli powder\n</br>
 <br>-A pinch of hot spice powder\n</br>
 <br>- A little oil\n</br>

 <br>Method:\n</br>

 -Soak rice and pulses for 6 hours.
 - Finely chop the rice and pulses and grind in a blender.
 Mix salt, sugar and water in the mixture and keep it at normal temperature for another 7/8 hours.  It won\'t be too thin, it will be a lot like a cake cake.
 -Heat oil and boil five cumin seeds or whole cumin seeds in it.  Put onion in it.  Add a little fried potatoes and peas.  Keep frying with all the spices.  When the raw feeling of spices is removed, sprinkle coriander leaves and green chillies and take it down.
 - Now brush the oil in a non-stick pan and heat on low heat.  When the oil is hot, pour one handful of dosa making mixture into the pot and spread it thinly and round with a spoon around the pot.
 - The lower part of the dosa becomes light brown and the edges rise. In fact, it must be understood that the dosa has become.  Put potato puree in between.
 - Care must be taken while lifting the dosa.  If you want, you can wrap it round or keep it straight.  You can do three corners again.
 -Every time before putting the dosa mixture in the pot, the pot should be wiped with a cloth and brushed with oil.  Otherwise the dosa will get stuck and tear during lifting.
 -Serve hot dosa with roasted pulses, vegetables, tamarind or olive chutney, coconut sweet chutney, mango pickle or yogurt.</string>
</resources>